(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-17T01:09:10.719034",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
darkness will fade away ,
Darkness will fade away,
light will guide your way
hope has descended and
you are not alone
虹と雨が織り成す コントラスト
In the contrast woven by rainbow and rain,
絶望の終わりを 願う ように
I wish for an end to your despair.
ここにいるよ 歌っているよ
So here I am and here I sing
夜明けの果てを
for the dawn of a new day.
零れ落ちた 黄昏のエレジーコール
Shout out the elegy of twilight,
凍えた過去と 涙にさようなら
say goodbye to your icebound past and tears,
きっと despair 晴れるように 歌うから
because I'll sing away despair and brighten your skies,
そして make a wish 艶やかに飾るから
so make a wish and I'll put it on stage to captivate you.
darkness will fade away ,
Darkness will fade away,
hope will lead your way
i 'm here to chant the melodies for you
I'm here to chant the melodies for you.
月と星が彩る サテライト
Satellite colored by the moon and stars,
暗闇も君なら飛べるよ
you can fly through the darkness if you're with me.
夜だからこそ 輝ける光もあるでしょう
There must be light that can shine precisely because it's night.
忘れないで 君のためのセレナーデ
Don't forget, the serenade for you,
壊れかけた夢の続きを ここで見よう
let's see the continuation of the broken dream here.
' cause i found your story
'Cause I found your story,
time is running too fast and i 'm left behind in solitude
time is running too fast and I'm left behind in solitude.
虹と雨が織り成すコントラスト
In the contrast woven by rainbow and rain,
絶望の終わりを願うように
I wish for an end to your despair.
ここにいるよ
So here I am
歌っているよ
and here I sing,
夜明けの果てを
for the dawn of a new day.
零れ落ちた黄昏のエレジーコール
Shout out the elegy of twilight,
凍えた過去と涙にさよなら
say goodbye to your icebound past and tears.
きっと despair 晴れるように歌うから
Because I'll sing away despair and brighten your skies,
そして make a wish 艶やかに飾るから
so make a wish and I'll make it shine bright.
月と星が彩るサテライト
Satellite adorned by the moon and stars,
暗闇も君と なら飛べるよ
I can fly through the darkness if I'm with you.
夜だからこそ輝く光もあるでしょ
There must be a light that can only shine because it's night,
忘れないで君のためのセレナーデ
don't forget, it's a serenade just for you.
壊れかかけた夢の続きを ここで見ようよ
Let's see the continuation of a crumbling dream right here.
予感が聞こえる
I can hear it coming.
believe in destiny 約束を果たすから
Believe in destiny, because I will fulfill the promise,
いつか reunion 語りきれない時代で
someday at a reunion in an era we cannot fully tell of.
嘆きも後悔も笑い飛ばそうよ
Let's laugh away both grief and regret,
そんな轍に希望と名付けよう
let's name such ruts "hope".
きっと despair 晴れるように歌うから
Because I'll sing away despair and brighten your skies,
そして make a wish 艶やかに飾るから
so make a wish and I'll make it shine bright.
君だけの声と重なるように
So that it overlaps with your voice alone,
こんな世界だってそばにいるよ
even in a world like this, I'm right by your side.
darkness will fade away, 晴れるように歌うから
Darkness will fade away, so I'll sing so your skies clear,
そして make a wish 艶やかに語るから
and make a wish, and speak of it brilliantly,
君だけの声と 重なるように
so it blends with your voice alone.
こんな世界だって そばにいるよ
Even in a world like this, I'm right by your side.
darkness will fade away
IRyS will light your way
Our journey has only just begun right now
HiRyS! It's IRyS in 3D for hololive English! Woo!
Thank you so much guys for coming to my 3D showcase! どひらめに来てくださりありがとうございます！
Thank you so much guys for coming to my 3D showcase! Thank you for coming to see my 3D!
ああ！ I fell from a very, very high height, but I got wings, so I'm fine!
Ah! I fell from a very, very high height, but I got wings, so I'm fine!
落ちたけど全然大丈夫だよ！この素敵なステージ見てください！ Thank you please check out my beautiful stage in the middle of a big city,
I fell, but I'm totally fine! Please check out this wonderful stage! Thank you, please check out my beautiful stage in the middle of a big city,
and that beautiful red tower behind, yes! めっちゃ美しい赤いタワーとすごい めっちゃ都会です、アイリス都会っ子です、I am a city girl, very much city girl!
and that beautiful red tower behind, yes! It's a gorgeous red tower, super urban. IRyS is a city girl, I am a city girl, very much a city girl!
I'm going to be singing a lot of songs on this stage, I'm so excited! Alrighty! So this is just the start,
but if you have any thoughts about my 3D showcase, or if you want to, you know, tweet about it, please use the hashtag #3DRyS right here!
but if you have any thoughts about my 3D showcase, or if you want to tweet about it, please use the hashtag #3DRyS right here!
Yes, please use the hashtag, let's tweet it, let's go! There's going to be a lot of fun stuff. Alrighty then, I can move so much now!
Look at me, look at this beautiful IRyS movement! Anyways, I'm going to be singing a lot more. Uh, so let's get to it then, yeah? Let's get to the next song! Alright, 次の曲聴いてください！ Shangri-La
Look at me, look at this beautiful IRyS movement! Anyways, I'm going to be singing a lot more. Let's get to the next song! Please listen to the next song! Shangri-La
愚かでいいのだろう 見渡す夢の跡
It's okay to be foolish, to overlook the traces of dreams,
さよなら 蒼き日々よ
farewell, my azure days.
流れに身を任せ いつか大人になってゆく
Letting myself go with the flow, someday I'll become an adult.
流れに身を任せ
Letting myself go with the flow,
いつか大人になってゆく
someday I'll become an adult.
少しずつ汚れていく事なの？
Will I gradually become tainted?
ジンジン くる
Tingling, coming,
ジンジン する
tingling, going,
どーなってもかまわないよね
it doesn't matter how it turns out.
ジンジンして
Tingling, doing,
ジンジンきて
tingling, coming,
そーなってもかまわないよね
it doesn't matter how it turns out.
太陽の痕スレンダー
Marks of the sun, slender,
熱いルージュも溶けて
your hot rouge melts away too.
今までの君と
And up until now,
ちょっとMoodが違う
the mood with you is a bit different.
ねぇ禁断のフルーツ
Hey, the forbidden fruits,
誰のために齧った?
who did you bite them for?
ヒカリ浴びた瞳が
Your eyes bathing in the light
今変わった
have just changed.
恋はそれまでの
Love is something that
ルール破るもの
breaks previous rules;
Kissの迷宮も
a maze of kisses,
情熱もCheck it out
and passion—check it out!
二人だけがシャングリラ
Only the two of us are in Shangri-La,
一秒も待たずに君を好きになる
unable to wait a second to fall in love with you.
心はもうシャングリラ
Our hearts are already in Shangri-La,
きりがない鼓動にLuv grows up
Luv grows up in a boundless heartbeat.
熱帯Modeのグランブルー
A tropic mode's grand blue,
Romanticになりたい
I want to become romantic.
どんな女神さえ君の敵じゃないさ
No goddess at all is a rival to you.
天然色のバタフライ僕の胸を奪った
The naturally colored butterfly stole my heart.
どこまで綺麗に愛と呼べるまで
How beautiful until we can call it love?
近くなりたくてたぶん傷心も
Wanting to get closer, maybe heartbreak too,
ジェラシーもCheck it out
and jealousy—check it out!
抱きしめればシャングリラ
If we embrace, we'll be in Shangri-La,
ときめきは本気で君に加速する
my heartbeat really accelerates for you.
唇からシャングリラ
Shangri-La from your lips,
永遠に二人はLuv grows up
for us, everlastingly our luv grows up.
息が止まりそうな実はきっと誰にも渡さない
I'm sure I won't hand over this breath-stopping truth to anyone.
二人だけがシャングリラ
Only the two of us are in Shangri-La,
一秒も待たずに君を好きになる
unable to wait a second to fall in love with you.
心はもうシャングリラ
Our hearts are already in Shangri-La,
きりがない鼓動にLuv grows up
Luv grows up in a boundless heartbeat.
満ち足りた日々の制圧は
The subjugation of our fulfilled days
徐々不安ていになる
gradually becomes unstable.
傷を負ってでも羽ばたきたい願いよ
Even if we bear scars, this wish wants to take flight;
どの金でいいのだろう
what price is fine,
見渡す夢の中
looking across our dreams.
さよなら遠き日々よ
Farewell, distant days!
笑顔と引き換えに掴みたかった
What I wanted to grasp in exchange for smiles
愚かしくてから気づく尊いもの
is something precious realized only after acting foolishly.
幼い僕らは
We, when we were young,
まと外れだらけさ
were full of off-target mistakes.
満ち足りた日々の制圧は
The subjugation of our fulfilled days
徐々不安ていになる
gradually becomes unstable.
傷を負ってでも羽ばたきたい願いよ
Even if we bear scars, this wish wants to take flight;
どの金でいいのだろう見渡す夢の中
what money is fine, looking across our dreams?
さよなら遠き日々よ
Farewell, distant days!
笑顔と引き換えに掴みたかった
What I wanted to grasp in exchange for smiles
愚かしくてから気づく尊いもの
is something precious realized only after acting foolishly.
幼い僕らは
We, when we were young,
まと外れだらけさ
were full of off-target mistakes.
輝く空は無邪気さをよそに
The shining sky, pretending to be innocent,
すべてを知っていた
knew everything.
僕らは目指したシャングリラ
We aimed for Shangri-La.
欲望を抑え切れずにクソにまみれた
Unable to suppress my desires, mired in filth,
自由を求め続けた
I kept seeking freedom;
今なら言えるだろう
now I can probably say it.
ここがそう楽園さ
This is indeed paradise.
さよなら遠き日々よ
Farewell, distant days!
距離を置いてこそ
Only by keeping our distance
自由の大きさを知る
do we know the true magnitude of freedom.
未熟な心はそれさえ分からないまま
An immature heart doesn't even realize that;
今なら言えるだろう
now I can probably say it.
ここがそう楽園さ
This is indeed paradise.
さよなら遠き日々よ
Farewell, distant days!
輝く空は無邪気さをよそに
The shining sky, pretending to be innocent,
すべてを知っていた
knew everything.
僕らは目指したシャングリラ
We aimed for Shangri-La.
欲望を抑え切れずにクソにまみれた
Unable to suppress my desires, mired in filth,
自由を求め続けた
I kept seeking freedom;
距離を置いてこそ
only by keeping our distance
自由の大きさを知る
do we know the true magnitude of freedom.
未熟な心はそれさえ分からないまま
An immature heart doesn't even realize that;
今なら言えるだろう
now I can probably say it.
ここがそう楽園さ
This is indeed paradise.
せーの
Ready, go!
でもそんなんじゃだめ
But that's no good,
もうそんなんじゃほら
look, it won't work like that.
心は進化するよもっともっと
Our hearts will keep on evolving, more and more!
言葉にすれば消えちゃう関係なら
If words will ruin our relationship,
言葉を消せばいいやって思ってた
then I thought we could just erase the words.
恐れてただけどあれ?なんかちがうかも
Were you scared? But wait, something's not right!
千里の道も一歩から
A journey of a thousand miles starts with a single step,
石のようにかたいそんな意志で
with a resolution as firm as stone.
ちりも積もれば山となでしこ?
If dust piles up, does it become a nadeshiko?
しんぬきでいやしぬきで!
With all my might—no, ready to die for it!
ふわふわり ふわふわら
Fluffy and fluttering, fluttery and fluffy,
あなたが名前を呼ぶ
when you call my name,
それだけで宙へ浮かぶ
I can fly straight up into the sky.
ふわふわる ふわふわり
Fluttery and fluffy, fluffy and fluttering,
あなたが笑っている
when you smile,
それだけで笑顔になる
I'm affected by it and start smiling too.
神様ありがとう
Thank you, God!
運命のいたずらでも
Even if our fateful encounter was just a prank by fate,
めぐり逢えたことが幸せなの
I feel blessed just to have crossed paths with you.
でもそんなんじゃだめ
But that's no good,
もうそんなんじゃほら
look, it won't work like that.
心は進化するよもっともっと
Our hearts will keep on evolving, more and more!
そうそんなんじゃいやだ
Yup, I don't want it like that;
ねぇそんなんじゃまだ
hey, that's not enough yet!
私のこと見ててね
Keep looking at me forever and ever!
せーのっ
One, two...
でも そんなんじゃ だめ
But that's no good,
もう そんなんじゃ ほら
look, it won't work.
心は進化するよ もっともっと
Our hearts will keep on evolving, more and more.
言葉にすれば消えちゃう関係なら
If words will ruin our relationship,
言葉を消せばいいやって思ってた 恐れてた
then we won't need them... I was scared.
だけど あれ? なんかちがうかも..
But wait, something's not right...
千里の道も一歩から
A journey of a thousand miles starts with a single step.
石のようにかたい そんな意志で
So I'll go on with a resolution as firm as stone.
「し」抜きで いや 死ぬ気で!
With all my might—no, fighting for my life!
あなたが名前を呼ぶ それだけで宙へ浮かぶ
When you call my name, just that makes me float into the sky.
あなたが笑っている それだけで笑顔になる
You are smiling, and just that makes me smile.
神様 ありがとう 運命のいたずらでも
Thank you, God. Even if our fateful encounter was just a prank by fate,
めぐり逢えたことが しあわせなの
I feel blessed that we met.
でも そんなんじゃ だめ
But that's no good.
もう そんなんじゃ ほら
Look, it won't work.
心は進化するよ もっともっと
Our hearts will keep on evolving, more and more.
そう そんなんじゃ やだ
Yup, I don't want it like that.
ねぇ そんなんじゃ まだ
Hey, that's not enough.
私のこと 見ててね ずっとずっと
Just keep on looking at me, forever and ever.
私の中のあなたほど あなたの中の私の存在は
If you are as important to me as I am to you,
まだまだ大きくないことも わかってるけれど
I know that I'm still not very significant in your heart yet.
今この同じ瞬間 共有してる実感
Right now, the feeling that we are sharing this exact same moment together—
略して?ちりも積もればやまとなでしこ!
In short, it's accumulating like the Yamato Nadeshiko spirit!
あなたを見上げたら それだけでまぶしすぎて
When I look up at you, it's just too dazzling.
あなたを想っている それだけでとけてしまう
When I think about you, I just melt away.
神様 ありがとう 運命のいたずらでも
Thank you, God. Even if our fateful encounter was just a prank by fate,
めぐり逢えたことが しあわせなの
I feel blessed that we met.
コイスル キセツハ ヨクバリ circulation
The season of love is greedy circulation.
コイスル キモチハ ヨクバリ circulation
The feelings of love are greedy circulation.
コイスル ヒトミハ ヨクバリ circulation
The eyes of love are greedy circulation.
コイスル オトメハ ヨクバリ circulation
The maiden of love is greedy circulation.
あなたが名前を呼ぶ それだけで宙へ浮かぶ
You call out my name, and just that makes me float into the sky.
あなたが笑っている それだけで笑顔になる
You are smiling, and just that makes me smile.
神様 ありがとう 運命のいたずらでも
Thank you, God. Even if our fateful encounter was just a prank by fate,
めぐり逢えたことが しあわせなの
I feel blessed that we met.
私のこと 見ててね ずっとずっと
Just keep on looking at me, forever and ever.
ふわふわり ふわふわ る
Fluffy and fluttering, fluttery and fluffy.
あなたが名前を呼ぶ それだけで宙へ浮かぶ
When you call my name, just that makes me float into the sky.
ふわふわ る ふわふわり
Fluttery and fluffy, fluffy and fluttering.
あなたが笑っている それだけで笑顔になる
You are smiling, and just that makes me smile.
神様 ありがとう 運命のいたずらでも
Thank you, God. Even if our fateful encounter was just a prank by fate,
めぐり逢えたことが しあわせなの
I feel blessed that we met.
神様 ありがとう 運命のいたずらでも
Thank you, God. Even if our fateful encounter was just a prank by fate,
めぐり逢えたことが しあわせなの
I feel blessed that we met.
めぐり逢えたことが
The fact that we met
しあわせなの
is such happiness.
でも そんなんじゃだめ
But that's no good.
もう そんなんじゃほら
Look, it won't work.
心は進化するよ もっともっと
Our hearts will keep on evolving, more and more.
そう そんなんじゃやだ
Yup, I don't want it like that.
ねぇ そんなんじゃまだ
Hey, that's not enough.
私のこと見ててね ずっとずっと
Just keep on looking at me, forever and ever.
Phew, that was two songs in a row!
Let's go, Shanti La and Renai Circulation! Woo!
Ah, I hope you guys liked this.
I really like the gap between the two songs, you know, Shanti La from Kanaria, watch Kanaria, bam is like bam! And then Renai Circulation is like ooh, azatoi.
I really like the gap between the two songs, you know, Shanti La from Kanaria, watch Kanaria, bam is like bam! And then Renai Circulation is like ooh, cute.
All righty, then. Now that after singing two songs, I think it's time to welcome our very first guests!
All righty, then. Now after singing two songs, I think it's time to welcome our very first guests!
Welcome, my friends from Hololive English Council!
Congratulations 3DRys!
So cute!
Thank you! We're so glad!
All righty, guys, please introduce yourselves one by one.
Who's going first? Me? You go first?
What's up? It's Ouro Kronii from Hololive English Council, the Warden of Chaos. Congratulations on 3D, IRyS! Thank you so much!
All righty, next up. Who wants to go next? Me? Yes, me. Okay, you, you go, you.
Oh, hi! Oh, hi! I'm Ceres Fauna from Hololive English Council, and IRyS looks so nice today!
Thank you, Fauna! All righty, then next, who wants to go next?
Oh, fauna, it's me fauna! IRyS, I'm obsessed with you right now! Really? I feel like a princess of my dreams!
Really? A princess?
Oh, Hime! Oh, Hime! Oh, Hime! The way you say hime sounds, sounds a little sarcastic. Thank you.
All righty, then last but not least, Ouro Kronii— wait, Tsukumo Sana from Hololive English Council, the Warden of Time— wait, the Avatar of Space!
really, really liked your Shangri-La.
Thank you!
You're so out there! Thank you so much!
Crazy translation. It's so cute!
Thank you guys! Alrighty then,
since I have you guys here, we are going to play a game with Iris, yes.
since I have you guys here, we are
going to play a game with IRyS, yes.
A game! A game that will test my acting skills. Yes!
A game! A game that will test
my acting skills. Yes!
It is called the- Let's test Iris's acting school game.
It is called... let's test
IRyS's acting school game.
Yeah, we didn't think of a name. Alright!
So first off, I will take some of the most iconic Japanese food, which is of course, sushi and green tea! Yes!
So first off, I will take some of the
most iconic Japanese food, which is
of course, sushi and green tea! Yes!
Oh my god, thank goodness, I was getting hungry.
Oh my god, thank goodness,
I was getting hungry.
I know, I ate a sandwich, but I'm going to eat sushi after this... during this, yes.
I know, I ate a sandwich, but I'm going
to eat sushi after this... during this, yes.
Alright, so for sushi, we have tuna,
or the maguro. Is the sushi showing up anytime soon?
or the maguro. Is the sushi
showing up anytime soon?
Cast a spell! Magic sushi spatching... magic spell! Bibbidi-bobbidi-boop sushi!
Cast a spell! Magic sushi spatching...
magic spell! Bibbidi-bobbidi-boop sushi!
Bibbidi-bobbidi-boop!
Oh, there we go! It worked! She's a magic princess!
Oh, there we go! It worked!
She's a magic princess!
She is a magic princess!
Oh my goodness, gigantic. Thank you. Yeah, we're going to eat a lot of sushi today.
Oh my goodness, gigantic. Thank you.
Yeah, we're going to eat a lot of sushi today.
Alright, so there's the maguro,
and then there's the ika, the squid.
Um, I'll eat them one by one, but one of those two has a huge buttload of wasabi in it,
Um, I'll eat them one by one, but one of
those two has a huge buttload of wasabi in it,
while the other one doesn't. But I'm going to try hard and pretend—
while the other one doesn't. But
I'm going to try hard and pretend—
actually, I'm going to pretend that both of them have a lot of wasabi in it, yes.
actually, I'm going to pretend that both
of them have a lot of wasabi in it, yes.
And you're supposed to guess which one actually had the wasabi in it. Yes.
And you're supposed to guess which one
actually had the wasabi in it. Yes.
Okay, okay, okay, okay. First off, first off, I'm going to eat the maguro.
Okay, okay, okay. First off,
first off, I'm going to eat the maguro.
Well, you're starting already? Oh, she's doing it already? Okay, it's easy to read, guys. It's fine.
Oh, you're starting already? Oh, she's
doing it already? Okay, it's easy to read, guys.
Uh, is that her body language? Yeah. Oh, oh, oh.
Uh, is that her body language?
Yeah. Oh, oh, oh.
Okay? Okay? Okay? Oh, serious? Is she super real? Okay?
Okay? Okay? Okay? Oh, serious?
Is she super real? Okay?
What? Okay. Okay. That is pretty convincing. That is really convincing. It is pretty convincing.
What? Okay. Okay. That is pretty
convincing. That is really convincing.
Oh, the sniffling! The sniffling! Pay attention! Pay attention, guys! Is that her sniffle?
Oh, the sniffling! The sniffling!
Pay attention! Pay attention, guys!
She's on her- she's on her knees. Okay? Is this too much? Is this super dramatic?
She's on her— she's on her knees.
Okay? Is this too much?
She thinks I'm overreacting. I'm overreacting! Aftertaste, holy shit! Okay, okay, okay, okay.
She thinks I'm overreacting. I'm
overreacting! Aftertaste, holy shit!
Which is like analyzing her when she could be in pain. But her body movements...
Which is like analyzing her when she
could be in pain. But her body movements...
That was convincing. That was maguro.
Okay, now we're going to have the squid. Squid.
Okay, now we're going to
have the squid. Squid.
Okay. Let's show.
Oh. That was quickly, quickly. I think that was too quick.
Oh. That was quickly, quickly.
I think that was too quick.
I think that was too quick. Because, like, you know, when you eat wasabi—she's back up.
I think that was too quick. Because, like,
you know, when you eat wasabi—she's back up.
Yeah, I think... her nose doesn't sound blocked this time either.
Yeah, I think... her nose doesn't
sound blocked this time either.
You know how, like, when you sneeze near that? There should be like that sound. Oh, she's overreacting. That's too much.
You know how, like, when you sneeze near that?
There should be like that sound. Oh, she's overreacting.
Oh, no, the squid is going somewhere. Oh, why is she sniffling so much now?
Oh, no, the squid is going somewhere.
Oh, why is she sniffling so much now?
Are you overly aware? I mean, I'd still be sniffling even if this wasn't the one that had the wasabi.
Are you overly aware? I mean, I'd still be
sniffling even if this wasn't the one.
Even if perhaps this didn't have the wasabi, I'd still be sniffling.
Even if perhaps this didn't have
the wasabi, I'd still be sniffling.
Because the first one was so wasabi. Yes. You're sniffling. Okay, guys, yes! Yes, which one had the wasabi in it?
Because the first one was so wasabi. Yes.
You're sniffling. Okay, guys, yes! Which one?
I'm going to go with maguro first. Yeah. Tuna.
I'm going to go with maguro first.
Yeah. Tuna.
Maguro. Final answer?
Yep, tuna. Yep.
All right, then. I guess I'll take that then. Drumroll, please.
Alrighty, then. I guess I'll
take that then. Drumroll, please.
Bam! Bim! Boop! Yes!
So the wasabi was in the maguro! It was a lot of wasabi. Holy smokes! Are you kidding?
So the wasabi was in the maguro!
It was a lot of wasabi. Holy smokes!
Like the moment I swallowed it, I was like, "Oh, shit. I'm done." I was crying. Okay.
Like the moment I swallowed it,
I was like, "Oh, shit. I'm done."
All righty, then. Uh, you guys, so if you get the right answer, you get to request a pose from me. So request a- are we going to get a pose each? Uh, no, one pose from all of you, like.
Alrighty, then. Uh, you guys, so if you get
the right answer, you get to request a pose!
Oh, just one. Do you have any ideas? Any ideas? Any, any of you? Any... I'm—
Oh, just one. Do you have any ideas?
Any ideas? Any, any of you? Any...
I have one, if no one else has one.
Ooh.
You go.
You go, you go.
Me? Okay.
All right, I don't know exactly what this pose is,
but it has a name.
Uh, mermaid pose?
Whatever.
Mermaid pose? Is that-
Mermaid pose?
There's no reference? Mermaid pose? No reference?
Mermaid pose? I'm just going to go with the name.
I have nothing to give you, just based off of the name, yeah.
Come on, we need to see Mermaid RyS.
Give us your best mermaid.
Okay. Okay.
Oh, this is a mermaid.
Oh, this is a mermaid! There's probably no legs, right?
So, um-
Pretend that I don't have legs, it's fins.
Can you make the flapping more sexy?
Yeah.
You look like a fish, you literally look like a fish out of water!
I am a magnificent- Where's the mermaid part?
You're not the 7th mermaid here!
All right, that was- that was my mermaid pose.
This doesn't look right.
Was it accurate?
Was that exactly what you were thinking?
Thank you.
Sure, it was around there, yeah.
All right, then. Next up.
It would have been nicer or sexier-
Matcha! Matcha! Shut up! Shut up!
Okay. Okay, first-
one of the tea is very bitter while the other one probably not, so we're going to try it out, yeah?
I'm going to pretend that both are equally bitter, so it's the same trick, okay?
Guess which one was actually bitter.
Okay, starting with the Yunomi.
Pick it up with her hand.
Yeah.
Ah, that was refreshing.
Okay, nice.
Now, we're going the other round.
Okay.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, okay.
It was- it was very, very nice to eat this after some spicy sushi.
Ah, that was good.
You just eat this?
I'm drinking it!
She's nervous!
She's lying!
She made it- Oh, my god!
See, I'm taking- I took another sip from this one.
Okay, that was my first one.
Okay, next one, second one from the glass.
B?
TB?
Ah, that's some mother- some good tea, too.
It tastes slightly different, but I honestly can't tell the difference between these two.
Nice refreshment after singing.
Which one do you guys think it is from my reaction?
They both look great.
Great tea.
I think it's the first one.
I think it's the first one, too.
What makes you think that?
Because you took a second sip of the second tea without being prompted.
I didn't prompt the second one, either!
As in, like, you didn't prompt the second one, you just went for a second sip.
But the first one, you were like- you had to- you made it very clear, like, "Oh, I'm taking a second sip now from the first one."
Oh, no, I just thought it was because it was the second time, that's why, for the second one, that's why I thought it was unnecessary to prompt.
It also uses-
She's really trying to convince us.
You also-
You guys have free opinions! Free opinions!
She also poured slightly longer for the first one.
True, you know what?
I'll take another sip for the- for the first one.
You heard that?
She's really trying to convince us that that's not the first one.
I don't know.
I think it's the first one.
I think it's the second one.
Can you- can you drink the second one again?
Oh, that had a little throat-gurgle though.
Now, you know when you drink something bitter, you have like that gag reflex and your throat goes like all weird.
Her throat went weird for like a split second.
I feel like she's playing mind games!
Dottchi daro na? Dottchi desho ne? Dottchi ga nigai no kana? Dotchi dotchi dotchi dotchi.
All righty, which one?
I'm fine with mid-are. I'm actually not that sure.
I'm not sure either.
I think it's the- might be the second one.
Maybe it's the second, yeah.
Final answer?
I think second.
Second.
All righty, then.
You guys got it right the first time!
What is sexy princess pose?
I'll do it real quick if you want.
I wanted- oh.
We'll do sexy princess pose.
Um- um- um- um- um- um- um- um-
This one?
Sexy princess?
Sexy princess pose?
What is sexy princess pose?
Whatever pose you do?
Yes, yes, more. Yes.
Oh yes.
Perfect, yes. Perfect.
So beautiful.
Yes, oh nice.
Oh, yes. Yes, yes.
I'm such an angel. You guys got it wrong, but still I still answered your please.
All righty then. Thank you for the split?
Huh? What? Splits?
You do splits? No, real quick.
No, shut up.
Real quick, no.
No, don't, no. No, no, no, I'm not. No.
No, no, shut up. You guys, we're running out of time, guys.
We're running out of time. It's not because I can't do a split or anything, it's because we actually don't have...
Oh, she's running away.
Yeah, nice. She's running away. All right.
We actually don't have much time. All right.
Yeah, thank you guys so much for coming. That was fun. That was fun.
Oh, god. It was it was so...
Thank you for having us. Thank you.
Thank you guys. Congratulations. You're doing an amazing job.
Yeah, keep it up. Keep it up. Keep it up.
We're all cheering for you.
Thank you. San doesn't come back up. Bye-bye. Bye-bye. Bye-bye Iris.
Iris? You don't have to say that, Iris.
All righty then. That was fun.
Well, but looks like we don't have much time.
Our next guest is showing up. Our next guest from JP! JP, we gotta go guest them out.
Toyoshimasu ja.
Ja, chotto aisatsu shini iko ka. Ne? Let's go say hi to her and go change, yeah?
Okay, let's go, meter. Be right back!
魅惑を隠す箱 秘宝に香る危険な Dangerous Marine Smell
A box hiding allure, fragrant danger in secret treasure, Dangerous Marine Smell
誘うガーネットの赤 極上の海賊の秘宝
The alluring red of garnet, the ultimate pirate's treasure,
それは私 艶が溢れ漂う 香りをどうかしら怖がらないで
That is me, overflowing with allure. Don't be afraid of the scent,
開けてみて
try opening it...
Sexy世界一 Superピチピチ
Sexy number one in the world, Super perky!
ぶっちぎり船長捕まえたくない？
Don't you want to catch runaway Captain?
You’re gonna get the treasure
Maybe tasting me
私の甘さが 欲しいんでしょ
You want my sweetness, don't you?
Ah-hoy！！Da-ba-da-boi
Ah-hoy!! Da-ba-da-boi
秘宝の鍵を
The key to the treasure
優しく刺して
Gently pierce it
宝庫の扉 マジで早く開けて
Open the vault door, seriously, open it fast
じれったい貴方の手 海図にこぼす甘いため息のTease
Your impatient hands, the sweet sigh of tease spilled on the chart
純紅のバラが しおれる前に WE WILL SAIL THE SEVEN SEAS
Before the crimson rose withers, WE WILL SAIL THE SEVEN SEAS
Summer sun smiling with glee
Shining ocean of marine
Now please grant my dearest dream
Open up this box
Open it right now or I will scream
泣く子も圧倒 naughty 誘惑ビーム 君たちももう我慢できなくなるよね
Even crying kids, overwhelming naughty temptation beam, you guys can't hold back anymore either
You’re gonna own the pleasure
Maybe love of me?
私のすべてを 手に入れて
Get all of me
金銀財宝
Gold and silver treasure
端た金でしょ
Is small change, right?
幸せにはいになっちゃう 誰か助けて
I'll become happy, someone help me
マジで遠慮しすぎ 君たち何考えての 分かってるんだわ
Seriously holding back too much, what are you guys thinking, I know it
渇望だから今すぐ開けてよ 宝箱 あなたを待つガーネット…
It's a craving, so open it right now, treasure box, the garnet waiting for you...
誘うガーネットの赤 コンパス片手に旗を掲げ
The alluring red of garnet, raising a flag with a compass in hand
この海をジャックしよ (Ah-hoy!)
Let's jack this ocean (Ah-hoy!)
やたらついておいで 共謀よ騒げ
Follow along eagerly, let's make noise together
最高の日々 (Ah-hoy!)
The best days (Ah-hoy!)
野郎ども ドラゴンが揚ネ
Lads, the dragon is raised...
船室はロマン、ボロマイハウスで夢を見て
Cabin is romance, dreaming in Voromai house
踊る ahoy! 見鳴る ahoy!
Dancing ahoy! Sounding ahoy!
同じ ahoy なら飲まなきゃ損々
If it's the same ahoy, you lose if you don't drink
1 2 3 ba-ba-bam
熱く語ろうよ架空 思いを解き放て
Let's talk passionately about fiction, unleash your feelings
赤くきらめくファッション 形から入るタイプで
Red glittering fashion, the type that starts with appearance
発射十秒前 走れガチ恋でしゃ
10 seconds before launch, run with serious love
夕焼けも照れるわ キラキラ
Even the sunset gets embarrassed, glittering
人間汗のしたたる女だけど
I'm a woman dripping with human sweat, but
噛み付く 船長はセンシティブだと
Biting? Captain is sensitive, so
バンされちゃうのですね (Hanya~)
You'll get banned, right?
奪われたら取り戻せ それが宝箱
If it's stolen, take it back, that's a treasure box
疾風怒涛 君たちとならたどりつける伝説のエルドラド
Storm and stress, with you guys we reach the legendary El Dorado
夜空を楽しくね 舞台よほらパーリナイ (Ah-hoy!)
Enjoy the night sky, stage look, party night (Ah-hoy!)
この世界で一番可愛いよ
You're the cutest in this world!
絶景が君を待つ
Spectacular scenery awaits you
伝説のエルドラド
Legendary El Dorado
夜空を楽しんでよ
Enjoy the night sky
舞台よほらパーリナイ (Ah-hoy!)
Stage, look, party night (Ah-hoy!)
この正気
This sanity
大切な仲間よ
Precious comrades
歌え踊れ騒げや騒げ
Sing, dance, make a fuss
踊る ahoy! 見鳴る ahoy!
Dancing ahoy! Sounding ahoy!
同じ ahoy なら飲まなきゃ損々
If it's the same ahoy, you lose if you don't drink
1 2 3 ba-ba-bam
宝箱 あなたを待つガーネット…
Treasure box, the garnet waiting for you...
宝箱のMarine
Marine of the treasure box
世界で一番可愛いよ
You're the cutest in this world!
滅茶苦茶メツガキ
Messy brat
エロガキ エロガキ エロガキ
Perverted brat...
番きゅう番きゅう姉ちゃんパンツ何色？
Ban Q ban Q, big sis, what color are your panties?
お宝 お宝 お宝 お宝
Treasure, treasure, treasure, treasure
まずい まずい まずい まずい どうでも、ストップ！
Bad, bad, bad, bad, whatever, stop!
なれまっすトップ！
Become the top!
ド・キ・ド・キ・し・て rouge ?
Do-ki-do-ki-shi-te rouge?
いきづきますよーっ！
Breathing heavily!
無罪！ 無罪！ 美少女無罪！
Not guilty! Not guilty! Innocent beauty!
マリン！ マリン！ マリンは無罪！
Marine! Marine! Marine is not guilty!
やっぱりキラキラ もっとクラクラ
Still sparkling, more and more dizzy
ねえ、言ったよね？
Hey, you said it right?
年齢なんて関係ないってさ
That age doesn't matter at all
そういうめんどくさいのも
Even those troublesome things
含めて愛してくれるって
You'll love me including all of that
ねえねえ、言ったよね？
Hey hey, you said it, right?
ふーん、そういうこと言うんだ
Hmph, so that's how it is
ちなみに この船では
By the way, on this ship
美少女無罪が適用されるけど！？
Innocent beauty applies here, you know!?
まかせて！ 魔法で若返り
Leave it to me! Rejuvenated by magic
ヒミツの素顔はキミにだけ
My secret bare face is just for you
トクベツですよー！？
It's special, okay!?
あぁ… アタシ厄介 よ
Ah... I'm a handful
あぁ… 港 なんじゃ
Ah... not a port
はしゃげないわ 最近はね
Can't get too excited lately
宝の島にしてほしい気分
Feeling like making it a treasure island
出航ーー！！
Set sail!!
キュートは正義 美少女無罪
Cute is justice, innocent beauty
キミの一番目指してヨーソロー！
Aiming for your number one, yosoro!
本当は自信ないけど頑張っちゃう
I'm actually not confident, but I'll do my best
ahoy！！
Ahoy!!
きゅっ きゅっ きゅるん
Kyu kyu kyurun
きゅっ きゅっ きゅるんるん
Kyu kyu kyurunrun
恋する気持ち 17歳
A loving feeling at 17 years old
０時にになっちゃうワ オトナの時間
Turning 12, adult time
やっぱりキラキラ もっとクラクラ
Still sparkling, more and more dizzy
ド・キ・ド・キ・し・て rouge ?
Do-ki-do-ki-shi-te rouge?
まだ早い ♡
Too early ♡
だっ だっ だめ です か ！？
No, no, is that bad!?
フリル の 服装 着 たら
If I wear frilly clothes
そんな こと 、 ないよ
There's no such thing
だっ だっ だってば
No, no, because
魔法少女 に なって みたい
I want to become a magical girl
ギリギリ 有罪 ! ?
Verging on guilty!?
進路 は なん なん 星
Our course is Nannan Star
ちょっぴり 足ん ない 積極 性 ？
A little lacking in assertiveness?
結局 キミ も もっと 若い 子 ？
After all, do you prefer younger girls?
なんだって する から
I'll do anything, so
見捨て ないで 、 キミ たち ！
Don't abandon us, everyone!
ちょっと イイ トコ 見 て みた ぁ い ！
I want to see some cool sides of you!
あぁ … たまに いじけ ちゃう
Ah... sometimes I get sulky
あぁ … それでも いい の ？
Ah... is even that okay?
年頃 だ もん 本気 に し ちゃう
I'm at that age, so I'll take it seriously
嵐 の 中 も 一緒 に 、 行こ う ！？
Let's go together even through the storm!?
出航 ー ！！
Set sail!!
ハート に チャーム 美少女無罪
Charm on heart, innocent beauty
あれ あれ どー し た ！？
Huh, huh, what happened!?
めんどさい よ なんて 言っちまっ て
Saying "what a pain"
かまって くれる キミ が 好き
I love that you pay attention to me
完全形を口に出すと シケてしまいそうだから
Because if I say the complete form out loud, it feels like it'll dampen the mood,
音でかき消そう 無駄なものを気にしないでふざけ合いたい
I want to drown it out with sound, and joke around without worrying about useless things.
どんなに凄い本や映画より 色あせない不滅の日々を重ねて歩きたい
I want to walk stacking up undying days that never fade, more than any amazing book or movie.
stand by you いつも stand by you
Stand by you, always stand by you,
涙のターミナル uh uh 並んで立っている
at the terminal of tears, uh uh, standing side by side.
stand by you いつも stand by you
Stand by you, always stand by you,
未来がハイになる uh uh 君と歌になる
the future gets high, uh uh, becoming a song with you.
stand by you oh oh 眠らない街の喧騒を抜け出して yeah
Stand by you oh oh, slipping out of the sleepless city's hustle, yeah
stand by you oh oh 光溢れた夢の続きは君と共に
Stand by you oh oh, the continuation of light-filled dreams is with you.
名無しの感情持ち余すと 上手く笑えなくなるから
If I have too much nameless emotion left over, I won't be able to smile properly,
一緒に燃やそうその想いを 語り尽くして笑い合いたい
so I want to burn those feelings together, talk it all out and laugh together.
どんなに凄い賞や順位より 君のそばに居られることが1番誇らしい
More than any amazing award or rank, being able to stay by your side is my proudest thing.
stand by you いつも stand by you
Stand by you, always stand by you,
涙のターミナル uh uh 並んで立っている
at the terminal of tears, uh uh, standing side by side.
stand by you 息を切らせていく 期待で汗ばんでいく
Stand by you, losing my breath, sweating with expectation,
uh uh 君と明日へ行く stand by you oh oh
uh uh, going to tomorrow with you, stand by you oh oh,
瞬きも忘れるほどの幸せで yeah
with happiness so great I forget to blink, yeah
終わらせかけした話の先が生まれ始める
the continuation of nearly-finished talks begins to be born.
たとえ僕ら遠く離れた場所へ行こうとも 変わらずにいたいよね？ yeah
Even if we go to a far-off place, we'll stay unchanged, right? yeah
変わるはずがないよね？ yeah
There's no way we'd change, right? yeah
stand by you いつも stand by you
Stand by you, always stand by you,
涙のターミナル uh uh 並んで立っている
at the terminal of tears, uh uh, standing side by side.
stand by you いつも stand by you
Stand by you, always stand by you,
未来がハイになる uh uh 君と歌になる
the future gets high, uh uh, becoming a song with you.
stand by you oh oh 眠らない街の喧騒を抜け出して yeah
Stand by you oh oh, slipping out of the sleepless city's hustle, yeah
stand by you oh oh 光溢れた夢の続きは君と共に
Stand by you oh oh, the continuation of light-filled dreams is with you.
光りあふれた日々の続きを 君と共に
The continuation of days filled with light, with you.
どんなに凄い笑いあいたい
No matter how amazing, I want to laugh together
しょうがないというより 君のそばにいられることが
Rather than it can't be helped, being able to stay by your side
一番誇らしい stand by you いつも stand by you
is my proudest thing. Stand by you, always stand by you
涙のターミナル uh uh 並んで立っている
at the terminal of tears, uh uh, standing side by side.
stand by you いつも stand by you
Stand by you, always stand by you,
未来がハイになる uh uh 君と歌になる
the future gets high, uh uh, becoming a song with you.
stand by you oh oh 眠らない街の喧騒を抜け出して yeah
Stand by you oh oh, slipping out of the sleepless city's hustle, yeah
stand by you oh oh 光溢れた夢の続きは君と共に
Stand by you oh oh, the continuation of light-filled dreams is with you.
息を切らせていく 期待で汗ばんでいく
Losing my breath, sweating with expectation,
uh uh 君と明日へ行く stand by you oh oh
uh uh, going to tomorrow with you, stand by you oh oh,
瞬きも忘れるほどの幸せで yeah
with happiness so great I forget to blink, yeah
終わらせかけした話の先が生まれ始める
the continuation of nearly-finished talks begins to be born.
たとえ僕ら遠く離れた場所へ行こうとも
Even if we go to a far-off place,
変わらずにいたいよね？ yeah 変わるはずがないよね？ yeah
we'll stay unchanged, right? yeah, there's no way we'd change, right? yeah
stand by you いつも stand by you
Stand by you, always stand by you,
涙のターミナル uh uh 並んで立っている
at the terminal of tears, uh uh, standing side by side.
終わらせかけた話の先が生まれ始める
The continuation of nearly-finished talks begins to be born.
たとえ僕ら遠く離れた場所へ行こうとも
Even if we go to a far-off place,
変わらずにいたいよね？ 変わるはずがないよね？
we'll stay unchanged, right? There's no way we'd change, right?
stand by you
WoW!WoW!Standing by you wow~ wow~
WoW! WoW! Standing by you, wow~ wow~
伝えたい感情のイメージ弾んでる声で届く
The image of feelings I want to convey reaches you with a bouncing voice.
覗く未来はいつでも君の声が聞こえた
Peeking into the future, I could always hear your voice.
シンパシー感じてみて(いつでも)
Feel the sympathy (Always)
想いはクリティカルかな(ここに)
Are our feelings critical? (Right here)
君と見た群青がそっと明日へ響いて
The ultramarine blue we saw together softly echoes toward tomorrow.
On my way すれ違う on my way~
On my way, passing each other On my way~
心一つに standing by you
With one heart, Standing by you
何度も何度も雨のち後悔でも
No matter how many times, even after rain and regret,
君となら進めるの
I can move forward if I'm with you.
More Bravely輝いていて長い旅
More Bravely, shining brightly on this long journey,
夢の狭間で視線と紡ぐ
weaving gazes in the narrow space of dreams.
今日を歩いていたいみたい
It feels like I want to walk through today.
ただここから暗闇さえも
From right here, even the darkness
七色に描けるように
can be painted in seven colors.
Way to goこれ遠くで見えないから way to go~
Way to go, because it's too far to see, Way to go~
一緒に行くって決めたんだよ
I decided we're going together.
WoW!WoW!Standing by you wow~ wow~
WoW! WoW! Standing by you, wow~ wow~
輝く青色ステージくるりと空は踊る
A shining blue stage, the sky dances in circles.
歩く先はいつでも君の絶対ストーリーじゃないか
Isn't the path ahead always your absolute story?
And that was Ahoy! With Houshou Marine-senpai and... Standing by you!
Thank you so much, Marine-senpai, for singing "Ahoy!" with me.
I've always wanted to sing "Ahoy!" ever since... ever since I got into Hololive, so I'm really happy I got that wish granted.
Thank you so much! And "Standing by you," my favorite song from Hige Driver-san.
Hige Driver-san's original song is so cool, super cool! Ah...
And guess what? Time flies!
Like, I can't believe it, it was just like daytime, just a few minutes ago, now it's already nighttime!
Look at how pretty this is! The moon is out, a humongous moon!
It looks like it's going to crash into Earth anytime soon. And the sky is very clear.
Look at the stars. I'm so glad the weather is nice today, no rain whatsoever. If there was rain, the show would've been cancelled, damn it.
Thank God the weather gods have blessed me.
It's beautiful. Oh, wait? Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait?
I thought I told you guys to stay home!
My little friends, Gloom and Doom, are here! Oh, they're so cute! Let me introduce you to them. Um, this one is Gloom. This one is Gloom, say hi to camera, Gloom.
Oh, kawaii ne! And, and this one is Doom. They're still cute mascot characters! Kawaii ne!
Eh, thank you guys so much for coming. Ah, is there anything you guys want me to do with Gloom and Doom today?
The chat? Chat, I'm watching you.
Any sort of pose you want me to do with them? I'll take maybe one request 'cause we're running out of time.
One request, if I could see it in the comments.
Hmm? Punch them? Did I see a comment to punch them?
Am I going to punch them? You're going to take it, right? You're going to take it, right? Okay.
Ha! Okay. I'm sorry. Sorry, sorry. This is for—this is fan service. There's nothing else I can do. Okay. You're going to take it good, yeah? You're going to take it. Okay.
Ha! Hey.
All righty then. Now I'm done with you two. I'm done with you two. That was great. They were great punching bags. I'm sorry, I'm sorry. Here's a big hug, big hug, big hug.
Oh, no, no, you're scared. No, no, no. It's okay, big hug, big hug. I'm sorry.
You guys are fun, you guys are—you guys are very soft. You guys can handle it, we're fine. All righty then, thank you guys so much for coming, Gloom and Doom.
I think it's about time you guys go rest, yeah? Especially now that you got that—that big—that big wound on your face. Bye! Bye, Risu! Bye-bye, Risu!
Alrighty then, we're getting to the end of the guest part, but there's one more guest, one more special guest we have.
Let's welcome our final guest today with a song.
常世の闇に囚われたまま 奏でる悲鳴を (聞かせて)
Imprisoned in eternal darkness, playing the cries of sorrow (Let me hear them)
さあ 爪を磨いたら まだ子供のようなあなたのために
Now, once you've sharpened your claws, for you, who are still like a child,
ああ 試されたいなら その愚かな手に手錠をかけて
Ah, if you want to be tested, put handcuffs on those foolish hands.
常世の闇に囚われたまま
Trapped in the eternal darkness,
奏でる悲鳴を 聞かせて
play your wails and let me hear them.
さあ 爪を磨いたら まだ子供のようなあなたのために
Now, once you've polished your claws, for your childish self...
あぁ 試されたいなら その愚かな手に手錠をかけて
Ah, if you want to be tested, put handcuffs on those foolish hands.
常世の闇に囚われたまま 甘い甘いガムを噛んでた
Trapped in the eternal darkness, chewing sweet, sweet gum.
いくつもの後悔を捧げて
Offering up countless regrets,
さりげない合図に隠された
hidden within a casual signal—
答えはすぐにわからせてあげる
I'll make you understand the answer right away.
微笑な嘘にまみれた
Immersed in a smiling lie,
拒んだままに 受け入れてあげる ほら悲鳴を聞かせて
just as you refused, I'll accept you—now let me hear your cries.
さあ 指を鳴らしたら この子猫のような私のために
Now, once you snap your fingers, for this kitten-like me...
あぁ 喉が渇いていたわ 薄紅の口に指を散らして
Ah, my throat was parched, scattering fingers across pale crimson lips.
狭い牢獄に閉じ込められたまま 首輪に繋がれたいの?
Trapped inside a narrow cell, do you want to be chained by a collar?
くだらないルールじゃ奪えない 自由はこの手の中にある
Freedom that useless rules can't take away is already in these hands.
愛情では計れない 弱ったままに選ばせてあげる ほら心を開いて
Unmeasurable by affection, I'll let you choose while you're weak—now open your heart.
わからないふりをして寝ぼけてるの? もっと熱い暗闇を見せてね
Are you playing dumb and sleepwalking? Show me a more passionate darkness, won't you?
さりげない合図に隠された
Hidden within a casual signal—
答えはすぐにわからせてあげる
I'll make you understand the answer right away.
微笑な嘘にまみれた 拒んだままに 受け入れてあげる
Immersed in a smiling lie, just as you refused, I'll accept you.
自由はすでにこの手の中にある
Freedom is already in these hands...
愛情では測れない 弱ったままに選ばせてあげる ほら心を開いて
Unmeasurable by affection, I'll let you choose while you're weak—now open your heart.
開いて
Open it.
分からないふりをして ねぼけてるの? もっと熱い暗闇を見せてね
Are you playing dumb and sleepwalking? Show me a more passionate darkness, won't you?
ね
Hey...
さりげない合図に隠された
Hidden within a casual signal—
答えはすぐにわからせてあげる
I'll make you understand the answer right away.
微笑な嘘にまみれた 拒んだままに
Immersed in a smiling lie, just as you refused,
受け入れてあげる ほら心を
I'll accept you—now open your heart.
歪むこの名を 刻ませてあげる
I'll let you carve this distorted name—
ほら 悲鳴を
now let me hear your cries.
わからせてあげる ほら 秘密を 聞かせてよ
I'll make you understand—now let me hear your secrets.
夢見ないで ほら聴かせて
Don't dream, just let me hear it.
はい 今のは桃鈴のファクトでした
Yes! That was Momosuzu's "FACT."
そして本日最後のゲストの桃鈴です ごしゅいーん
And today's final guest is Momosuzu! Goshuin!
ぷりぷり ギャグ星の音とか聞こえたもんです
Puripuri, sounds like gag star noises, right?
いやー ということでアイリス スルディ改めておめでとう
Anyway, IRyS, Suisei, congratulations once again!
ありがとう 今日来てくれて本当に入りありがとう
Thank you so much for coming today!
呼んでくれて嬉しかった しかもとわの曲のねファクトを歌ってくれて嬉しかったよ
I was so happy you invited me, and I was so happy you sang Towa's song "FACT"!
絶対歌いたかった これマジでかっこいい マジで
I definitely wanted to sing it. This is seriously so cool, seriously!
え しかもさデビュの時もねパレットね 歌ってくれたもんね
And you know, when I debuted, you sang "Palette" too!
そう 2回目 もう何と2回目
That's right, for the second time! Can you believe it, a second time?
嬉しい
I'm so happy!
じゃあ ということはとわもアイリスの曲をカバーしないとね
So that means Towa has to cover one of IRyS's songs, right?
いや ややそのプレッシャー プレッシャーをかけて
No, no! Don't put that pressure on me!
えでもかそしていいの?
Eh, but can you do it?
あah もちろんぜひぜひ聴きたい 聴きたいよ
Ah, of course! I'd definitely love to hear it.
ということはいつかちょっと歌うわでヒーローしちゃおうかななんて思います
So I guess someday I'll try singing it and maybe make it a hero thing, I think!
はい はい はい
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
と ということは 実は この2人ちょっとどうですか 配信で2人っきりみたいなのは
So, actually... how is it for the two of us doing something just us two on a stream?
あんまないよね
We don't really do that, right?
ていうかむしろほぼない
In fact, almost never!
そう そうだよね
Yeah, that's true.
なんか大人数ではまああるけど 2人ではちょっとあまりないよね みたいな
Like, with a large group we do, but just the two of us, not really.
でも 実は結構遊んでたりして
But actually, we hang out quite a bit!
そうだよね みんな 実はね
That's right, everyone. Actually...
そうアフタヌーンティに狩りもいたけど狩りと言ったりとか
Yeah, we went to afternoon tea, and went hunting...
あれめっちゃ美味しかった 2人だけで夢の国連れってさ
That was so good! And you took me to the land of dreams just the two of us...
夢の国マジで感動したんだけどあのお城とか
I was seriously so moved by the land of dreams, especially that castle!
お城ね2人で見て
We looked at the castle together,
もういろいろいやこれはいいなって
and talked about how nice it was.
とたちもこんな感じでやりたいねなんて言って
We said we'd love to do something like this together too,
あとスプラッシュでびしょ濡れ
and got soaked on Splash Mountain!
そう びしょ濡れになったよね
Yeah, we got completely soaked!
マジで びしょ濡れなったよね
Seriously, we got so soaked!
あれ楽しかったよね 楽しかったね
That was so fun, right? It was so fun!
そう 意外とね 裏でね 裏というか配信外でちょっと遊んだりしてたんですよ
Yeah, surprisingly, behind the scenes—or rather, outside of streams—we've been hanging out a bit.
そう だから この こういうね 大きな場で なんかトワセッパと話すのなんかついすで すでいっちゃう感じがして
So, talking with Towa-seppa in a big venue like this makes me feel like I just keep rambling on.
いやいいよ すでで嬉しいよ
No, it's fine! I'm happy you ramble.
しかもちょっと 3Dで並ぶのも若干恥ずかしいところもあるの
Plus, standing side by side in 3D is also a bit embarrassing!
何言ってないすか トワセッパ可愛いじゃないすか
What are you talking about? Towa-seppa is so cute, right?
ありがとう スタイルがいい アイリスさんありがとうございます
Thank you! IRyS has such great style, thank you so much!
写真のスクリーンショットが目立ちますけど
Your screenshots stand out so much, though!
スクリーンショット可愛いよ
The screenshots are cute!
いいよ それ
That's good.
むしろそれがいい
Actually, that's better.
本当に？
Really?
むしろそれがいい
Actually, that's better.
ともあれアイスのいいな体 ともそんな感じでなりたいけど
Anyway, I want a nice body like that too.
ああそう これからいっぱい牛乳飲めばいいんじゃない？
Ah right, if you drink lots of milk from now on, right?
牛乳飲めば イェーイ！
Drinking milk! Yay!
まあそういうことでね この後もね歌うんだよね？
Well, with that said, we're singing after this too, right?
うん バリバリ歌います
Yup, singing hard!
じゃあ今日はね誘ってくれて本当ありがとう 本当に嬉しかった
So thank you so much for inviting me today, I was really happy.
こちらこそありがとう 本当に めちゃくちゃ一緒に歌えてマジで今後も とわ先輩みたいなの歌えるように頑張るわ
Likewise, thank you so much! It was so much fun singing together, I'll work hard to sing like Towa-senpai!
いやいや うれしい ありがとう
No no, I'm glad, thanks!
じゃあこの後もね ２人とも頑張って
Well then, good luck to both of us after this!
はい！で今日は呼んでくれてありがとう！ありがとう バイバーイ またね 今度ね頑張れ！
Yes! Thanks for inviting me today! Thank you, bye-bye! See you again! Do your best!
馬鹿みたい 子供なのね
I've been a fool, and you've been childish.
夢を追って 傷ついて
You fell down, you got hurt chasing sweeter dreams.
嘘が下手くせに 笑えない笑顔見せた
Never could hide the truth in your eyes, that's how I knew that smile was a lie.
I love youも ろくに言わない
"I love you" is something you never say,
口下手で ほんまに不器用
Couldn't get it out, always so clumsy.
なのになのにどうして サヨナラは言えたの
So then why, please won't you tell me why, you could find the words to say goodbye?
だめだね だめよ だめなのよ
It's no use, no good, no good at all,
あんたが好きで 好きすぎて
I'm in love, still in love, still in love with you.
どれだけ強いお酒でも
Hard as I try, I can't even drink this pain away,
歪まない思い出が 馬鹿みたい
Memories of you, twisting my view, I've been a fool.
馬鹿みたい 本当バカね
I've been a fool, such a big fool,
あんた信じるばかりで
All I did was believe in your every word.
強い女のふり 切なみの夜風浴びる
Pretending I'm a strong woman, bathed in the lonely night wind.
一人になって 3年が過ぎ
Three years have passed since I became alone,
街並みさえも 変わりました
Even the streets have changed.
なのになのにどうして 未練だけ置き去り
Even so, why are only regrets left behind?
ほんまに ロクな男やない
You're really not a good man,
揃いの指輪 はずします
I'll take off our matching rings.
ざまあみろ せいせいするわ
Serves you right, good riddance.
いい加減 待ってても 馬鹿みたい
No matter how long I wait, it's just like being a fool.
だめだね だめよ だめなのよ
It's no use, no good, no good at all,
あんたが好きで 好きすぎて
I'm in love, still in love, still in love with you.
どれだけ強いお酒でも
Hard as I try, I can't even drink this pain away,
歪まない思い出が 馬鹿みたい
Memories of you, twisting my view, I've been a fool.
ほんまに ロクな男やない
You're really not a good man,
揃いの指輪 はずします
I'll take off our matching rings.
ざまあみろ せいせいするわ
Serve you right, I'm so glad!
なんなのよ この涙 馬鹿みたい
What are these tears? I'm such an idiot.
And that was Bakamitai!
You guys are probably wondering why Bakamitai, cause I wanted to sing it, that's why! I've always wanted to sing it.
Ah, that was good stuff.
All righty then, but we're... we're getting close to the ending, yes?
All righty then, but we're getting close to the ending, yes?
So I think it's about time we move... I think it's a really nice weather, nice night time. I think it's now time for a nice night drive toward the Arena, e-Arena! Let's go by car! So follow me, yeah, follow me! Woo!
So I think it's about time we move... It's really nice weather, nice night time. I think it's time for a nice night drive toward the Arena, the Arena! Let's go by car! So follow me, yeah, follow me! Woo!
Crazy for love
Crazy for love, crazy for love...
Crazy for love, shock!
Got to be the first one got to be the last one
You never get no peace of mind
Never show emotions all communication's over
You got no feeling
Stop it now guess you wonder why
You just sold out the dream inside
Up and down baby for your lovin'
Baby we can fly up to the sky
Every day every night crazy for love
Into the depth of desire
Every time everywhere crazy for love
And now my spirit's on fire
Every day every night crazy for love
Into the depth of desire
Every time everywhere crazy for love
And now my spirit's on fire
Crazy for love shock!
When you get that feeling when you find some lovin'
You've got to run away from here
Show me your emotion baby make me feel so natural
It's the real thing
Stop it now guess you wonder why
You just sold out the dream inside
Up and down baby for your lovin'
Baby we can fly up to the sky
Every day every night crazy for love
Into the depth of desire
Every time everywhere crazy for love
And now my spirit's on fire
Every day every night crazy for love
Into the depth of desire
Every time everywhere crazy for love
And now my spirit's on fire
Crazy for love shock!
When you get that feeling when you find some lovin'
You've got to run away from here
Show me your emotion baby make me feel so natural
Baby make me feel so natural
It's the real thing
Stop it now, guess you wonder why
You just sold out the dream inside
Up and down, baby for your lovin'
Baby, we can fly up to the sky
Every day, every night, crazy for love
Into the depth of desire
Every time, everywhere, crazy for love
And now my spirit's on fire
Every day, every night, crazy for love
Into the depth of desire
Every time, everywhere, crazy for love
And now my spirit's on fire
Crazy for love
Got no feeling
Stop it now, guess you wonder why
Up and down, baby for your lovin'
Every day, every night, crazy for love
Every time, everywhere, crazy for love
Into the depth of desire
And now my spirit's on fire
Crazy for love
How was that drive?
I had a wonderful time with you guys,
and we are here in one piece!
One piece, no harm whatsoever, we did not crash into anything.
One piece, no harm whatsoever,
we did not crash into anything.
Very safe, very fast drive, and here we are at the Eean Arena, woo!
Very safe, very fast drive,
and here we are at the Eean Arena, woo!
Ah, that was great.
And I sang so much,
I'm getting a little tired.
I kind of think I need a drink.
Let me get that drink.
Ooh!
And what else would I drink than this? The HOPE Soda!
Ah, that's good stuff.
Isn't it cute? I love the can, it's so cute.
This is like the best soda on Earth.
Maybe a lot of you guys haven't tried it, maybe a lot of you guys don't have it,
Maybe a lot of you guys haven't tried it,
maybe a lot of you guys don't have it,
it's okay, because the merch today will be able to make up for it somewhat.
Because even if you don't have your own HOPE Soda, bam!
HOPE Soda Can SleeveRyS (Can Sleeve)
You can use this HOPE Soda Can SleeveRyS to turn your run-of-the-mill old soda into HOPE Soda.
You can use this HOPE Soda Can SleeveRyS
to turn your run-of-the-mill old soda into HOPE Soda.
At least feel like you're drinking HOPE Soda, let's go.
Isn't it cute?
The nice refreshing red pink and the cool black strap, yes.
The nice refreshing red pink
and the cool black strap, yes.
Keep your drink chill and your hands drip-free, yay!
So, byRyS the sleeveRyS, I mean B-U-Y RyS, buy the sleeve, let's go.
Alrighty.
It's really been reaching towards the very, very end.
It was a long journey, over two years since debut, and we're finally here with my 3D showcase.
It was a long journey, over two years since debut,
and we're finally here with my 3D showcase.
Becoming 3D was one of my big reasons why wanting to join Hololive,
Becoming 3D was one of my big reasons
why wanting to join Hololive,
and actually being able to stand here doing this 3D, it's all thanks to you guys and your support.
and actually being able to stand here doing this 3D,
it's all thanks to you guys and your support.
Thank you so, so, so much.
It's been a long two years and we're here, but it's the start of a new page, and here's to many more years to come!
It's been a long two years and we're here,
but it's the start of a new page,
and here's to many more years to come!
Yay!
Well, I think it's time for the final song? Saigo no ikyoku ni naru no kana?
Well, I think it's time for the final song?
Saigo no ikyoku ni naru no kana?
Saigo no ikyoku ni naru ka na, doudaro?
Who knows, maybe you guys might want an encore, or maybe you guys want me to just hurry up and get...
Who knows, maybe you guys might want an encore,
or maybe you guys want me to just hurry up and get...
Please listen to my final song, my original song, Berserker!
蔓延る不協和音 混沌のShow
The spreading dissonance, a chaotic show
耳を塞いでも 搾取された日常
Even if I cover my ears, an exploited daily life
立ち上がれ 理不尽に喘いでも
Stand up, even if we gasp in absurdity
何人たりとも此処は 奪わせないよ
No one can ever take this place away
私が私であることが 私自身の正義だから
That I am myself is my own justice
I know どんな結末になっても
I know, no matter what the ending is
後悔は1ミリもない
There is not even a millimeter of regret
Burn up 怒髪天衝いて 燃え盛れ
Burn up, pierce the heavens, burn fiercely
想いを懸けて Everything
Cast your feelings, everything
I'm a Berserker
塵と化せ 有象無象
Turn to dust, phenomenal and noumenal
私の世界は 私のモノ 掲げるのは 希望
My world is my own, what I raise is hope
Absolute leader 高らかに
Absolute leader, loudly
Absolute leader 目覚めよ今 Wake up
Absolute leader, awake now, wake up
並べ立てられたご都合主義 噛みつき剥ぎ取り 弱者は強者のPrey
Lined up convenience, biting and tearing away, the weak are the prey of the strong
立ち上がれ 不条理に泣いても
Stand up, even if I cry over unreasonableness
何人たりとも此処は 侵させないよ
No one can ever take this place away
私は私の言葉で 私自身と歩いてゆく
I am walking with myself in my own words
I know どんなに嗤われたって
I know, no matter how much I'm bitten
恥ずべきことはない
There is nothing to be ashamed of
Don't stop 進み続け 何度も生まれ変わりながら Fearless
Don't stop, keep moving forward, being reborn over and over, fearless
I'm a Berserker
蹴散らして 有象無象
Kick aside, phenomenal and noumenal
私の世界は 私のモノ 揺るがない真実を
My world is my own, the unshakeable truth
Absolute leader 燦々と
Absolute leader, brilliantly
Absolute leader 目覚めよ今 Wake up
Absolute leader, awake now, wake up
Burn up 怒髪天衝いて 燃え盛れ
Burn up, pierce the heavens, burn fiercely
想いを懸けて Everything
Cast your feelings, everything
I'm a Berserker
塵と化せ 有象無象
Turn to dust, phenomenal and noumenal
私の世界は 私のモノ 掲げるのは 希望
My world is my own, what I raise is hope
Absolute leader 高らかに
Absolute leader, loudly
Absolute leader 目覚めよ今 Wake up
Absolute leader, awake now, wake up
アンコール！アンコール！アンコール！アンコール！
Encore! Encore! Encore! Encore!
えー、そこまでみんな言うなら、しゃーないな！
Geez, if everyone says that, I have no choice!
Please listen to my last song for today, One Last Kiss.
初めてのルーブルは なんてことはなかったわ
My first love was nothing special
私だけのモナリザ もとっくに出会ってたから
My own Mona Lisa, we had met long before
初めてあなたを見た あの日動き出した歯車 止められない喪失の予感
When I first saw you, the gear that started moving that day, an unstoppable premonition of loss
もういっぱいあるけど もう一つ増やしましょう
There are already so many, but let's add just one more
Can you give me one last kiss?
忘れたくないこと
Something I don't want to forget
Oh oh oh oh oh...
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh...
忘れたくないこと
Something I don't want to forget
Oh oh oh oh oh...
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh...
I love you more than you’ll ever know
I love you more than you'll ever know
写真は苦手なんだ
"I'm not good at taking pictures,"
でもそんなものはいらないわ
but I don't need things like that.
あなたが焼き付いたまま
With you still imprinted vividly
私の心のプロジェクター
on the projector of my heart.
寂しくないふりしてた
I pretended I wasn't lonely,
まあ、そんなのお互い様か
well, I guess we're both like that.
誰かを求めることは
To yearn for someone
即ち傷つくことだった
was to end up getting hurt.
Oh, can you give me one last kiss?
燃えるようなキスをしよう
Let's share a fiery kiss.
忘れたくても
Even if I wanted to forget,
忘れられないほど
it's so unforgettable that...
Oh oh oh oh oh...
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh...
I love you more than you’ll ever know
I love you more than you'll ever know
Oh oh oh oh oh...
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh...
I love you more than you’ll ever know
I love you more than you'll ever know
もう分かっているよ
I already know,
この世の終わりでも
even at the end of this world,
年をとっても
even as we grow old,
忘れられない人
you're an unforgettable person.
An unforgettable person,
忘れられない人
an unforgettable person...
Unforgettable person,
忘れられない人
unforgettable person...
Unforgettable person,
忘れられない人
unforgettable person...
Unforgettable person.
I love you more than you'll ever know
忘れられない
Unforgettable...
忘れられない人
Unforgettable person,
unforgettable person...
I love you more than you'll ever know
吹いていった風の後を
Chasing after the wind that blew past,
追いかけた 眩しい午後
on that dazzling afternoon.
Thank you so much for coming everyone!
みんな来てくれて、ありがとう！
Thank you all so much for coming!
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!